https://www.earthsunmoon.com/esmpolicy.php#employment

Social Distancing
Excuse Me...
Star Wars Themed
Advice From...
Social Distancing
Excuse Me...
Star Wars Themed
Advice From...
×
Sign up to receive our emails and get 10% off your first order!*
You will receive a welcome email with a promo code.
Make sure you check your 'promotions' or spam folder.
*Offer valid for first-time email subscribers only.
Policies and Info
If you cannot find all of the information you need on our site, please don't hesitate to call us at 1-800-516-2584, or email us at retail@earthsunmoon.com. We are in the office Monday through Saturday from 9 a.m. to 9 p.m. EST.
Payment Options
You may order by Credit Card (Visa, Master Card, American Express or Discover) or by Money Order or Check. We also accept PayPal for online orders.
Canadian Customers- all payments must be in US funds or by credit card.
Mail order customers- may pay by check, money order or credit card.
To order by mail, print out and complete our ORDER FORM. Mail to: Earth Sun Moon Retail, 111 N Center St, Grove City, PA 16127
Checks that you write for payment to our company may be converted into an electronic debit.
There will be a $30.00 service fee for any money order or check returned to us from the bank for any reason.
We collect sales tax on orders shipping to any state where Earth Sun Moon has a physical presence (Pennsylvania) or is otherwise required to collect tax by law.
Our website will charge you the correct state and local sales tax by delivery address.
Items sold that are shipped to destinations in the following states may be subject to tax:
Arizona*
Arkansas*
California
Colorado*
Connecticut*
Georgia*
Idaho
Illinois*
Shipping
We only ship to U.S. states, Canada and APO/FPO/DPO addresses. Sorry, but we cannot ship international orders. All orders ship from our location in Grove City, PA via USPS.
Expedited (overnight) shipping is not available to Alaska, Hawaii, P.O. Boxes, Canada or APO/FPO/DPO addresses.
Please keep in mind that clearing customs may delay orders shipping to Canada by 2-3 weeks. APO/FPO/DPO orders may be similarly delayed.
Standard Shipping Rates
Up to $20.00 ............... $5.95
$20.01 - $35.00 ......... $6.95
$35.01 - $49.99 ........... $7.95
$50.00 or more ...........FREE
Rush Shipping Rates
Add $4.95 to Standard Rate
Overnight Shipping Rates
Add $23.95 to Standard Rate
Orders placed after NOON EST on Fridays will not be shipped until Monday.
Canadian Shipping Rates
Up to $20.00 .................... $9.95
$20.01 - $35.00 .............. $14.95
$35.01 - $60.00 .............. $24.95
$60.01 - $85.00 .............. $34.95
$85.01 - $105.00 ............. $39.95
$105.01 - $155.00 ............ $42.95
$155.01 - $205.00 ........... $45.95
$205.01 - $300.00 ........ $47.95
Over $300.00 ................... $49.95
Sizing Info
Most T-shirts and long sleeve tees are heavyweight, pre-shrunk 100% cotton.
However, sports grey and all heathered t-shirts are cotton/poly blend.
Sweatshirts are a heavyweight 50/50 cotton/poly blend.
Hats are embroidered, garment stone-washed, 100% cotton twill
and feature a cloth strap with antique brass buckle closure.
Click for ALL ITEMS sizing guide.
×
T-Shirt Sizing Guide
Exchanges/Returns
We hope it never happens, but if you're not 100% satisfied with your purchase we will accept returns and exchanges as long as the items are in re-sellable condition 						(i.e. clean, not worn or laundered, original tags attached, etc.). Remember to include payment for price differences and upsizing (e.g. from kids to adult sizes, from short-sleeve to long-sleeve styles). We are not responsible for items lost in transit to us. Defective items, mis-shipments or shortages need to be reported within 14 days of receiving your order by calling 1-800-516-2584. These items will be replaced at our expense.
Print an Exchange/Return Form
Discounts
Free standard shipping on orders over $50.
Applies to US Shipping only.
Privacy Policy
We take the privacy of our customers seriously. This privacy policy governs the data-handling for Earth Sun Moon Trading Company and its wholly-owned subsidiaries, Alumni Originals and Ink Pixi, and applies to all web sites: www.earthsunmoon.com, www.aotees.com, www.inkpixi.com.
Our offices are located at 111 North Center Street in Grove City, PA 16127 USA, and you can reach us at (724) 458-1687 extension 315 with questions or concerns about your personal information.
OUR POLICY
Our web sites do not collect personally-identifiable information from individuals unless they provide it to us voluntarily and knowingly. So, if you just want to browse and learn about our unique shirts and hats, we invite you to do so. As a casual, unregistered visitor to our site, we'll recognize your home server (e.g., that your web access is through AOL.com), but not your e-mail address or any other personal or system information. Of course, since we must ship our shirts and hats to you, if you want to order our products it will be necessary for you to provide personally-identifiable information. This will include your name, address, phone number and credit card information. Any information you provide is downloaded off of the web server to a secure system and is maintained there. We do not knowingly collect personal data from children and will, if requested to do so by a parent or guardian, suppress a child's personal data in our database.
We have implemented security policies, rules and technical measures to protect the personal data that we have under our control from unauthorized access, improper use or disclosure, unauthorized modification, unlawful destruction, and accidental loss. All our employees and data processors who have access to, and are associated with the confidentiality of our visitors' personal data, have undergone background checks, and are obliged to respect the confidentiality of our visitors' personal data.
OUR CUSTOMER LIST
When you buy our products, we add your information to our Customer List. We may use this list to follow up with you about an order, and may from time to time send you mail to let you know about new products or services we think you would like. This information may also be shared with other marketers to bring you offers of interest. If you prefer not to receive mailings from these companies or from us, please advise us by using the mail address, e-mail, or phone number provided above. Please include your name and address, and we will place you on our Do Not Mail list.
E-MAIL INFORMATION
If you purchase from us online, you will be required to supply us with your e-mail address. This is not optional, because we use this to provide you with an order confirmation and then with a shipping confirmation. You may, however, also choose to receive periodic e-mails from us; we may inform you of new products or web-only promotions. If you do provide us with your e-mail address you can rest assured that we do not provide your e-mail address to anyone else.
ACCESS TO PERSONAL DATA
Our customers have voluntarily provided all the information that we have on file, while placing their orders. This includes name, address, phone number and e-mail address if provided. All credit card information is encrypted for security purposes.
If you have concerns about the content of the personal information we have on file for you, please call us at (724) 458-1687 extension 315. We will confirm the information that you provided to ensure our records are accurate. We reserve the right to refuse to confirm personal data, but will give a reason for our refusal.
Employment Opportunities
Download our Job Application here.
Please, help us improve your experience. Click here to take our short feedback survey.
Are you shopping for a nature lover? Well, you've come to the right place to find a quirky t-shirt! We've been going at this since 1996 - making quality shirts and hats while providing a large selection of original designs. You will see that most of our designs feature animals, or outdoor themes such as camping, hiking, gardening and fishing. Trust us! We can make your gift-giving a success for just about any occasion, even if it's just a treat for yourself!
If you're looking for a completely original design, we can help! Pay a visit to our sister company at www.esmprintworks.com and you can design your own original apparel or start with a wide variety of templates.
Product Categories
Newest Designs
Youth
Women
Animals
Outdoor Activities
Star Wars Themed
Holiday
